Viewers all over the world, prayer is a work of faith.
Have faith in God.
All things are possible; have faith in God.
Today, many of us pray but perhaps, not prayer of faith.
Have faith in God; all things are possible.
This means, only faith counts.
Faith comes when we allow the Word of God to dominate our heart.
Tell your neighbour,
Faith comes when we allow the Word of God to dominate our heart, our spirit.
I can sense God touching you right now.
Viewers, wherever you are, I can sense God touching you right now,
in Jesus Christ's name!
Only faith pleases God.
Say to the Lord, touch me, Lord.
Let all spirits in your life leave, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of stagnation, spirit of affliction, spirit of rejection, spirit of failure, spirit of hardship -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
I have decided to follow Jesus
No turning back
Let all spirits operating in your life leave, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of stagnation, spirit of failure, spirit of setback, spirit of barrenness, spirit of affliction -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
Are you on the sickbed?
I command that affliction to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
I command that bed of affliction – leave, in the name of Jesus!
Be it in your bones, kidneys, liver – wherever in your organs – leave, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, sickness, disease, leave, in the name of Jesus!
What manner of man is Jesus
Hallelujah
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
I cover your business, career, future, family, marriage with the Blood of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
This is habit.
I want to tell you a little about my habit.
Habit is a gift from God.
Constantly pray in your heart.
As I am talking to you, there is prayer going on.
As I am looking at you, there is prayer going on.
Constantly pray – prayer without ceasing
in hymns, spiritual songs in your heart.
At the beginning, it may be very difficult
but as you continue, the Lord comes into the matter, helps to do it for you.
To show your genuine willingness, you have to start on your own.
Peter said, “I want to come with You, Lord, on the sea”.
He said, “Come!”
Peter was thinking that from the beginning, Jesus would help to carry him spiritually
but Peter moved on his own.
As he moved on his own, he found himself drowning – going down the sea.
When he was about to disappear, only his hand remained up in the sea.
Jesus realised, "Oh no, that is genuine willingness".
I will make you fishers of men
If you follow Me
To make you a fisher of men,
you become a deliverer, healer...
People have problems; you remove their problems, you point them the way, "This is the way".
If someone is thirsty, you cannot give water, you cannot tell him the way.
If someone is hungry, you cannot give food, you cannot tell him the way.
When someone is thirsty, needs water and you give water, he will say, "Ah" -
"Where are you going? Take this way" - he will follow.
I will make you fishers of men
If you follow Me
This is Jesus for you.
You are to start, take my habit – constantly pray in your heart.
When you are doing this, it cannot affect any other thing you are doing.
You can still talk to your neighbour while you are doing that – constantly pray in your heart.
That is prayer in the power of the Holy Ghost.
This is what I do – I meditate day and night on the Word and whatever I do prospers.
Do that and see what will happen.
When you are going to work, you wake up in the morning,
"In the name of Jesus, in the Blood of Jesus..."
Even that is enough.
"In the name of Jesus, in the Blood of Jesus", in your heart.
And people would greet you, "How are you?" - "Fine."
"... in the name of Jesus, in the Blood of Jesus..."
What do you need the name of Jesus, the Blood of Jesus for?
For sanctification.
Our heart is so funny.
Flesh, spirit - there is so much conflict.
Your desire and God's desire - conflict.
There is so much division; "Steal - don't steal. Fight - don't fight. Help - don't help him. For and against" -
this is our heart.
To sanctify this heart and make it focused; just one focus, one way.
One way
Only one way to Heaven
I’m so glad
I’m so glad that Jesus is the Way
The way, not a way.
When your heart begins to say, "Go this way, that way" - you know there is trouble.
I meditate on the Word day and night.
When I say; “On the Word”,
I mean, constantly pray in my heart
in hymns - you have many hymns -
"Take more of me, give me more of You, oh Lord Jesus"
You should be busy with that.
Melody in your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are inviting Him; He will come at a time you are not expecting.
Once He takes over that heart, He will take control.
Yet, now, you are wrestling - there is so much conflict between this and that.
Take care of your heart – that is my habit.
You may stay with me for one day, you will not see me going to the prayer room to pray.
You will say, "Does it mean that he doesn't pray? But it is a prophet, I have not seen him today praying.
I have been seeing him moving around; he didn't even go on his knees to pray."
Oh, who told you I don't pray?
24 hours, 24/7 my heart is praying.
Hallelujah!
Viewers all over the world, please take care of your heart.
My habit – habit is a gift from God.
Pray without ceasing – constantly pray in your heart in hymns, spiritual songs,
make melodies in your heart to the Lord.
Everywhere is quiet, but hearts should engage in what?
In prayer.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 08/11/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 16/11/2018